往昔
Sammy受伤了
Sammy's hurt
他伤得很严重
He's hurt real bad
这条祈祷面向所有能听得到的天使
This one goes out to any angel with their ears on
我是Dean Winchester
This is Dean Winchester
我需要帮助
And I need your help
先告诉我你叫什么
Start with a name
Ezekiel
我有办法治好你弟弟
There's a chance I can fix your brother
怎么治
How will it work
我可以在自己疗伤的同时 治愈Sam
I heal Sam while healing myself
Sam可以随时驱逐我
Sam can eject at any time
如果Sam驱逐了我
And if Sam does eject me
他就会死
He will die
那咱们就把这事儿保密
Then we keep it a secret for now
我只希望
I just got to hope that
你是个好人
You're one of those good guys
我是
I am
Zeke
救救她
You gonna bring her back
就像你救活了Cass那样
Like you did with Cass
我不能这样做
I cannot keep doing that
为什么
Why the hell not
每次我使用能量
Every time I use my power
都会削弱我的力量
It weakens me
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas
爸爸想让我们继续他未竟的事业
Dad wants us to pick up where he left off
帮助别人 杀魔除怪
Saving people,hunting things
家族事业
The family business
Becky 我写的都是真的
Becky,it's all real
我就知道
I knew it
那是胸吗
Nipples
我们居然猎杀怪物
I mean,come on,we hunt monsters
我为什么会在这儿
Why am I here
正常人看见怪物会撒腿就跑
I mean,normal people they see a monster and they run
但咱们不可以 不要啊
Not us...no,no,no
咱们睁着眼睛往虎口里钻
We search out things that want to kill us
这是真的 是真的
It's real,it's real
你的死期到了
Now,you die
你知道什么人才这么干吗
You know who does that
神经病
Crazy people
我是蝙蝠侠
I'm Batman
我们脑子有病
We are insane
我把鞋丢了
I lost my shoe
太可怕了
That was scary
比赛只剩下一分二十秒了 现在是62比54
And with a 1:20 left in the game,it's 62-54
这一队很想获得冠军
This team wants that championship
很厉害
It would be great
他得分了
He's up
太棒了 但是裁判吹哨了
It's good,but the ref's on the whistle
他犯规了 应该是撞人了
He's calling a foul.It could be charging
十号 他可能对此不开心
Number 10,he's not happy about that
这家伙可能会被罚出场
This guy just about could foul out
除了裁判没人希望他被罚出场
And nobody but the ref wants to see that happen
Johnson教练看着时钟
Coach Johnson watching the clock
他要求暂停
He calls time-out
正在跟裁判说话
Talking to the ref right now
目前这场比赛中
You know,so far in this game
只有一名球员被裁判
There have been a number of fouls called
罚出场 而这不是
By this particular ref,and that's not
权利的游戏
别大惊小怪 Colonel
Easy,Colonel
谁在那儿
Is anyone here
每次都能吓着我
Gets me every time
怎么了 伙计
What's the matter,boy
是我啊
It's me
见鬼
What the hell
怎么了
What
Kevin
他刚给自己灌了水牛奶
Just poured some buffalo milk down his gob
两杯
Twice
水牛奶吗
Buffalo milk
对的 宿醉良药
Yeah.Hangover cure-all
里面什么都有
It's got everything in it
就是没有水牛奶
Except buffalo milk
他还没恢复过来吗
How's that kid still recovering from Branson
我能说什么 那小子太新手了
What can I say,he's a amateur
就在餐厅里喝的那两杯
The slippery nipple shot at the
差点儿要了他的命
Dolly Parton Dixie Stampede nearly killed the guy
好吧
All right
我找到了点儿东西
Well,I got something that's gonna
能让咱回归老本行
Get us back on the road
案子吗
A case
没错
Yeah
你确定你准备好了吗
You sure you're ready for that
我为什么没准备好
Why would I not be ready for that
你不是一直精神不大好吗
Aren't you kind of running on empty
但是在过去的3天里
Yeah,but the last three nights straight
我每天都能睡8个小时
I had eight hours of shut-eye
对于一个猎人来说 这简直超神了
And for a hunter,that's like 20
相信我 Dean
And trust me,Dean
我现在好极了
I feel good
那真是太好了 James Brown
Well,that's great and all,James Brown
但你还没从试炼里恢复过来
But you're still recovering from the trials
我觉得你应该慢慢来
I think you ought to pace yourself,you know
你恢复得越快
And the sooner you heal
然后呢
Yeah
我只是想让你早日恢复以前的状态
I just want you back to your old self
我已经好了
I am
Dean 听着
Dean,look
Kevin现在恢复正常了
Kevin's back on the heaven stoke
Crowley被咱们关起来了
Crowley's locked up
咱们应该做回自己的老本行
We should be out there doing what we do best
你到底想不想听
You want to listen at least
好极了
Okay,great
动物标本制作商
Taxidermist named Max Alexander
Max Alexander 被神秘撞死
Mysteriously crashed to death
身体几乎被完全肢解
Nearly every joint in his body dislocated
全身骨骼破裂
Every bone broken
完全变成了椒盐脆饼
Poor guy's a human pretzel
来说说什么东西能做到这种程度
You tell me what's got that kind of strength
神奇的墨西哥摔角选手
A demonic Luchador
那家店离咱们就几小时车程
Shop's a couple hours away
就在俄克拉荷马州的伊尼德 至少去查看一下
In Enid Oklahoma,we should at least check it out
除非你有充分的理由证明不应该去
Unless there's some reason you think we shouldn't
动物标本店 提供邮寄
真精致
Subtle
看看这个
Check that out
真是越来越诡异了
The creep factor just skyrocketed
你好
How're ya
Michaels探员和Deville探员
Agent Michaels and Deville
尸体已经被送去太平间了
Body's already been to the morgue
刚跟Dave Stephens聊过
Just wrapping up with Dave Stephens
是他发现了尸体
He's the one who discovered the body
我以前和Max一起打猎呢 真遗憾
Such a shame,I used to go hunt with Max
他人很好
He's real good egg
节哀顺变
Sorry for your lost
谢谢
Thanks
你不介意带我搭档四处查看一下吧
You mind showing my partner around
我有几个问题要问Stephens先生
I just got a couple questions for Mr.Stephens
没问题 跟我来
Okay,come on
你是Dave Stephens吗
Hey,Dave Stephens
如果你可以的话
I just got a couple questions for you
我有几个问题要问你
If that's all right
我会把你想知道的都告诉你的
I'll tell you whatever you need to know
Max他
Max was a
是个非常好的家伙
A real pal
结伴打猎吗
Hunting buddy
我猜的
Lucky guess
你是什么时候发现尸体的
So about what time did you discover the body
早上9点左右
About nine a.m.
是我提货的时间
At my usual pickup time
我每周三和周日
I come in every Wednesday and Sunday
都回来收内脏
To collect the entrails
收什么
The what
动物器官
The animal organs
Max把尸体剖开
After Max would dig'em out
然后制作标本
And work his magic
他
He
他是个艺术家
He was a real artist,you know
不过奇怪的是
Strange thing is,though
今天早上垃圾桶是空的
Bins were empty this morning
这怎么奇怪了
Why is that strange
因为今天是周日
Cause it's a Sunday
周末打猎 在这片区域来说
Weekend hunts are pretty much a
基本上是大丰收
Given in the neck of the woods
所以垃圾箱应该塞满内脏才对
So they're usually chock-full of guts
有没有可能是Max自己已经清理过了呢
Any chance Max could have cleaned them out himself
不可能
No
那东西有的有毒
It is a biohazard
你不能就这么轻易把它们清理干净
You can't just,you know,throw the stuffs out
得用火烧
You got to burn it
店里有没有其他东西报失
Is there anything else missing from the shop
没有
No
外来人员登记很完整 保险箱完好无损
The register was full and safe was intact
Max所有的作品都完好的待在墙上
And all of Max's trophies were still on the walls
除了你还有别人来过吗
Were there anybody else here when you showed up
没有了
No one
当然
Well,other than
除了 Colonel
The Colonel
失陪了
Excuse us
那么
So
咱们找到了个喜欢收集动物器官的贼
Okay,so we got a thief who's jonesing for animal parts
奇怪的符号
We got a pagan symbol
还有一块人肉卷饼
We get a human pretzel
是啊 这事儿很像是巫师干的
Yeah,it all sounds very witchy
但是我没找到任何巫术袋
But I wasn't able to find a hex bags
好吧 咱们再继续查一查
All right,well,let's keep digging
但是
But
不在这儿
Not here
我不喜欢它看着我的眼神
Don't like the way that one's looking at me
好了
Okay
那个涂鸦并不是巫术
Symbol in the graffiti,it's not wiccan
其实是个商标
It's copywritten
当地动物权益保护协会
Local Animal-Rights Group
伊尼德对PETA的回应
Enid's answer to PETA
注 PETA人道对待动物组织
S.N.A.R.T.
善待所有生物
开什么玩笑
You got to be kidding me
一群动物保护主义者跟标本制作商有仇
It makes sense that an animal-rights group
这事儿还挺容易理解的
Would have an axe to grind with a taxidermist
为什么
Why
那些动物本来就死了呀
The animal's already dead
是这样没错 但是猎人们可以继续
Yeah,but hunters are what
支持着整个行业
Keep them in business
现在的问题是
Now the question is
这帮动物保护主义者到底是巫师
Are those bleeding hearts actually witches
还是一帮乱涂鸦的小混混
Or just hippies
有什么区别吗
What's the difference
和谐地球 素食烘烤店
我就知道万恶之源
Always knew I'd find the source of all evil
会潜伏在素食店里
At a vegan bakery
什么味道
What's that smell
广藿香
A patchouli
注 常用于制作香水 香薰 杀虫剂 也是一味中药
混合着因为缺少肉食而产生的怨气
Mixed with depression from meat deprivation
嘿
Hey
知道什么人才在室内戴墨镜吗
You know who wears sunglasses inside
盲人
Blind people
和傻逼
And douchebags
是Olivia
Olivia
和Dylan Camrose吗
And Dylan Camrose
有什么能帮助您的吗
At your service
你们是S.N.A.R.T.的成员吗
You two are remembers of S.N.A.R.T.
事实上 是组织者和联合主席
Founders and co-presidents actually
有没有兴趣拿点儿资料看看
Can we interest you in some literature
或者来一块亚麻籽司康饼
Or a flaxseed scone
零谷物 零面粉 零糖分
It's wheat-free,gluten-free,sugar-free
-而且非常多汁 -给我打住
-And suprisingly moist -Let me stop you right there
我们是来调查
We're here to investigate
Max Alexander的死因的
The death of Max Alexander
当地动物标本制作商
A local taxidermist
他死了吗
He's dead
你认识他
You knew him
差不多吧
Ish
毕竟是个小镇
Small town
他昨晚被杀了
Well,he's murdered last night
S.N.A.R.T.的标志出现在犯罪现场
And the S.N.A.R.T. logo was found at the crime scene
你们俩不会恰好
You two wouldn't happen to
知道些什么内幕吧
Know anything about that,would you
他的业务都是靠猎人搞起来的
His business is funded by hunters
猎人都是一个德性
And you know how hunters are
一群自负的混蛋
They're selfish dicks
禽兽不如
Who define themselves by what they kill
作为倡议保护动物一员
And as animal advocates
我们无法接受他们的行为
We couldn't stand for that
所以你们杀了他
So you killed him
当然没有
Of course not
S.N.A.R.T.提倡零暴力
S.N.A.R.T. doesn't tolerate violence
零暴力就等于
This coming from a couple
散播恐吓涂鸦吗
Who spray paints death threats
那只是个提醒而已 我们就是想吓吓他
It was a scare tactic,we just wanted to spook him
但结果我们自己反被吓到了
Turns out we're the ones who got spooked
你什么意思
What does that mean
昨天晚上
Last night
我们俩碰头的时候
When we were tagging the joint
我们听到了一些动静
We heard this noise
嘶嘶的叫声
A hissing noise
我们吓坏了 然后跑进了巷子里
It freaked us out so we ran out into the alley
但是有人袭击了我们
But someone attacked us
把梅斯毒气喷进了我们的眼睛里
Sprayed us in the eyes with mace
但我俩不可能报警
And it's not like we could go to the cops
所以现在我们看起来像两个傻逼一样
So now we will look like total douchebags
因为我们在屋子里也戴着墨镜
Because we have to wear sunglasses inside
坏死病吗
Necrosis
细胞组织早亡
Premature death of tissues
所以他们的眼睛才变成了那样
That's why their eyes were all messed up
但并不是因为什么梅斯毒气
And it's not caused by mace
那是什么
All right then,what cause it
这儿写着呢
Right here
钝物敲击 射线侵染 毒液
A blunt force,radiation,venom
比如蛇的毒液
As in snack
那个标本制作商被勒碎了
The taxidermist was constricted
Olivia和Dylan听到了嘶嘶声
Olivia and Dylan heard hissing
然后眼睛被喷洒了液体
And they were sprayed in the eyes
毒液
By venom
那么
Okay,so
咱们要对付的
What are we talking here,some sort of a
是一只奇葩蛇精
Freaky-ass snake monster
有可能
Maybe
但是奇怪的是
The weird thing is
蛇要么是把猎物毒死 要么把猎物勒死
Snakes either envenomate or constrict
这两件事不会同时发生
No snake does both
那我更正一下
Correction
是巨奇葩蛇精
Freaky ass mega snake monster
可能是个Vetala干的
That could be a Vetala
是啊 但它们可直接上嘴咬
Yeah,but they're not afraid to sink their fangs in
标本制作商身上没有咬痕
Taxidermist was bite-free
跟valata习性不符
Doesn't really fit the profile
是啊
Right
那么
So
打给Kevin
So call Kevin
让他查查相关资料
Have him looked some stuff up
伊尼德动物收留中心
你是不是来早了
Aren't you early
老兄
Dude
你不是香水公司的吗
You said you were from a perfume company
不 不 不要啊
No,no,please
有爪痕
Claw marks
是啊 警察说所有的猫都不见了
Yeah,cops said all the cats went missing
好吧 昨天
Right,so yesterday
咱们对付的是个蛇精
We're dealing with some sort of a snake monster
今天成了猫咪杀手
Today it's a killer kitty
我不知道
I don't know
嘿
Hey
这个小家伙怎么这么眼熟
Why does that mutt look familiar
它是那个标本制作商的狗
That was the taxidermist's dog
所以 两处犯罪现场它都在
So he's been at both crime scenes
对
Yeah
也许它是嫌疑犯
Maybe it's a suspect
也许
Well,may
可能是化兽人 或许是变形怪
Could be a skinwalker,maybe a shapeshifter
我看不像
Doesn't really look like a monster to me
有办法试出来
One way to find out
嗨
Hi,boy
嘿
Hey
乖哈 不会痛的
This isn't gonna hurt at all
除非你被伤到
Unless it hurts
这么说
Guess we can
可以排除凶手了
Rule out killer
你们还需要帮助吗
You agents need any further assistance
警官 我们现在不需要 谢谢
Officer,I think we're okay.Thanks
随时可以找我
Let me know
警官 打扰一下
Officer,excuse me
能借用你的帽子吗
Can I borrow your hat
祝收养成功
Good luck getting adopted
这么说
So
Colonel不是嫌疑犯
The Colonel is not a suspect
它是目击证人
Maybe a witness
嘿 你懂手语吗
Hey boy,you speak sign language
-猴子才懂手语 -啊
-That's monkeys -Eh
这样吧
You know what
说出来可能很不可思议
This is gonna sound crazy
我读过一本书 讲一个男的
I read this book once about this guy
在一只狗目击一场凶杀案后
Who tried to teach his dog to speak
教狗说话
After it witnessed a murder
注 书名是The Dogs of Bable
成功了吗
It worked
没有
No
但是他还是写书了
But he wrote a book about it
没错 他没有我们手上的资源
Yeah,he didn't have what we have
Kevin 是我
Kevin,hey,it's me
怎么能和狗沟通
How do we speak to a dog
因纽特咒语
An Inuit spell
是的
Yeah
我们都知道 学者里面
We knew the...man of letters
也有爱斯基摩人
Had its own Eskimo section
这样就能跟Colonel无障碍沟通了吗
And it supposed to let us communicate with the Colonel
是的
Yeah,well
计划是这样的
That's the plan
Kevin说这像是某种
Kevin said it's like a sort of a
人与动物的思想融合
Human/animal mind meld
-什么意思 -如果成功
-Meaning -If it works
我们就能读懂Colonel的思想了
We should be able to read the Colonel's thoughts
好吧 我来
All right,I'll do it
-你 -你的麻烦已经够多了
-You -You got enough on your plate
比如
Like what
比如 你很疲劳
Like...you're tired
你还在恢复当中
You're on the mend,okay
还有
Plus,you
你的胃比较敏感 我们现在最不需要的
You got a sensitive stomach,last thing we need
就是你来喝这玩意儿
Is you chucking this stuff up
看起来不算太糟
It doesn't look so bad
我刚说错了
I was wrong
给我
All right,come on
咒语
Deila hér me
Dag eru nou rar vitur orum
好吧 那就赶快开始吧
All right,let's get this party started
告诉我你知道的所有事
Tell me everything you know
怎么不说话了
What's the matter?Cat got your tongue
好吧 不好笑
Tough crowd
给Kevin打电话
So,call Kevin
这咒语又不好喝 还一点用都没有
Spell tasted like ass and was a buzz
这都没影响到你的食欲 真棒
At least it didn't affect your appetite.Geez
换台
Change the station
快换台
什么
What
怎么了
你 你别说话 起作用了
You...shut up!It's working
赶紧问啊
Go
你再说一遍
Say it again
你管这叫经典摇滚乐吗
You call this classic rock
他们下一首就会放Styx的歌了
Next thing you know,they'd be playing Styx
Dennis Deyoung
And Dennis Deyoung?
只不过是朋克而已
A punk
Dennis Deyoung不是朋克
Dennis Deyoung is not a punk
Mr.Roboto是经典
It's Mr.Roboto,bitch
你为什么在跟一只狗
Why are you arguing with a dog
争论Styx乐队
About Styx
是哦
Yeah
嘿 亲
Hey boy
那个牛仔帽
What were you trying to tell us
你想告诉我们什么
About the cowboy hat
杀我最好朋友的蠢货
The douchewheel who killed my best friend
戴了一顶牛仔帽
Was wearing a cowboy hat
还杀了长发嬉皮士吗
And the pothead,too
对的
Yep
是同一个人作案
Same guy killed both
问问猫
Ask about the cat
那些猫去哪儿了
What about the cats
-我不知道 -我不想要这坨纸
-I don't know -I don't want this
我没看见多少
I couldn't seen much
我那个位置在收养所里又不是最佳观景区
I didn't exactly have the best view in the orphanage
但是我能闻出来
But I could smell him
那家伙身上有生肉的味道 洗洁精的味道
Guy reeked of red meat,dishwashing detegent and
还有万金油的味道
Tiger Balm
它说什么
So,what's he saying
说 那个凶手
That the...guy
有生肉的味道
He smelled like ground chuck
肥皂水
Soap suds
老妇霜的味道
Old lady cream
Dean 你在干什么
Dean,what are you doing
我不知道
I don't know
你笑什么
What're you laughing at
嘿
Hey
喂喂
Hey,hey
你
Yeah,you
说你呢
You
喂喂
Hey!Hey
你别跑 就你
You!You!You
你玩哪儿走 汪
You
呃 Dean
Ummmm,Dean
我觉得咒语成功了
I think the spell worked
但是 成功得有些过了
Fact,I think it worked a little too well
什么
What
你觉得 你可能 变成狗了
I think you might be a dog
-你说什么 -你挠你耳朵
-What -You're scratching your head
对邮递员吼
You're...barking at the mailman
还喜欢把扔出去的东西捡回来
You playing fetch
我
I
汪汪
Ruh-roh
不是 好
No,that...Okay
好的 谢谢
All right,thanks
所以说 这咒语是有副作用的
So,apparently the Inuit spell has some side effects
我喝之前怎么不说
Oh,it'd have been nice to know before I downed it
什么副作用
What kind of side effects
你跟动物思想融合的时候
When you mind meld with an animal,it's
有可能会表现出 该动物的习性
Possible to start exhibiting some of its behavior
别看我啊 Hoss
Don't look at me,Hoss
又不是我的错
It ain't my fault
我还有多久会想
How long am I gonna have the urge to
闻屁屁
Sniff butts
我才不想闻
I don't have the urge to sniff butts
现在不想
Yet
-你真的想 -没有
-Do you really have the -No
怎么可能
Come on
Kevin也不知道咒语会持续多久
Kevin doesn't know how long it'll last
你也知道 这不属于科学领域
It's not like it's exact science,you know
希望咒语失效之后
But hopefully when the spell wears off
副作用也随之而去
So will the side effects
我要是你 我就不吃
I wouldn't eat that if I were you
你真打算吃巧克力整死自己吗
Chocolate?Seriously
我们去哪儿
Where we headed
回收留中心去
Back to the shelter
闻线索吗
To sniff out more clues
还是挖漏掉的信息
Maybe dig up something we missed
你要再说犬界的双关
All right,one more doggy pun out of you
我就把你阉了
And I'm gonna have your nuts clipped
我不得不跟你说实话
I hate to break it to you
我已经寂寞空虚很久了
My sack's emptier than Santa's after Christmas
玩儿我呢吗
Oh,are you kidding me
滚开 蠢鸽子
Hey,dick move,pigeon
去死吧 脑残
Screw you,asshat
-它 -怎么了
-Did -What
等等 我是不是能听懂所有动物的话
Wait a minute,can I hear all animals
对啊 动物界的有通用语言
Yup,animals have a universal language
就像世界语
Like esperanto
这只就碰上了
But this one actually caught on
我才刚刚开始
And I'm just getting started,too
我要来个大的
Brewing a real big one
你的车过后肯定像糊了一层奶油一样白
Bet your ride's gonna look sweet in white
-它在说什么 -你
-What's he saying -You
这鸽子脑子有问题
He's being a douchebag
你说谁脑子有问题 脑残
Who you calling douchebag,douchebag
闭嘴 你这带翅膀的老鼠
Oh,shut it,you winged rat
-哥啊 -干什么
-Dude -What
你就 冷静一下
Just...calm down
上车吧
Just get in the car
哈哈 对啊
Ha,that's right,Sally
找妈妈哭去吧
Go cry to mama
够了 你这狗娘养的
That's it,you son of a bitch
Dean 快进车里
Ooh!Dean!Hey!Get in the car
我想把Colonel留在车里会比较好吧
I think it's probably best to just leave Colonel in the car
你说什么
Excuse me
窗户都是开着的
All the windows are open
你觉得我们喜欢那样吗
You think we like that
我们
We
你觉得就因为窗户是开的
You think because the windows are open
这就算是某种款待了是吗
That that's some sort of a treat,huh
狗跟我们一起进去
No,the dog's coming in
别那么冲
Respect
长得不错
Yeah,baby
没错
You said it
Dean
关于那个戴牛仔帽的男人
So,what else can you tell me
你还知道些什么
About the man with the cowboy hat
说实话 我看到的不多
Honestly,I couldn't see much
可恶的白内障
Damn cataracts
还没有人付我的手术费
And you know no one's going to pay for my surgery
只不过又是一起伤亡而已
Just another casualty of the system I guess
我不属于这里
I don't belong here,you know
我是纯种的
I'm pedigreed
我相信你很快就会出去的
Well,I'm sure you'll be out of here soon
别逗了 我都14岁了
Please,I'm 14
祝好运
Good luck...Ma'am
他们每天都要清理一次
Once the day they clean these cages
-每天一次 -好吧
-Once a day -Okay
我要吃饼干
Biscuit,Just one biscuit
我要拉寇儿薇芝的海报和摇滚乐
I need a Raquel Welch poster and a rock hammer
我要摇坏这栅栏
I'm shaking the fence,boss
我还在摇
Still shaking the fence
-我在这 -我是被陷害的
-Over here -I was framed
有发现吗
Any luck
基本没有
Hardly
没有任何线索
I'm not getting any clues
只是一堆抱怨
Just bunch of complaints
嘿 帅哥 过来
Hey,pretty boy.Over here
呃 很抱歉
Yeah,ummm,sorry pal
我今天的工作结束了
I'm done for the day
但是我什么都看见了
But I saw everything
我可以告诉你们 只是
And I'll tell you,but
不是免费的
It'll cost you
开什么玩笑
Wait,you kidding me
我要被一只狗敲诈了
I'm being extorted by a dog
你要什么
What do you want
要什么 希望被带走 还是要品牌世佳的食物
What?Beggin' strips?Snausages
那是婊子才要的好吗 如果我要告密揭发某人
Bitch please.If I'm gonna rat someone out
就必须是让我觉得值得的事
It's got to be worth my while
我要 挠肚子
I want...a belly rub
好吧
You...all right
不是你挠
Not from you,sweetie
要那个大个子
From that big one
那边
Over there
牛仔帽 皮裤
A cowboy hat,leather pants
这家伙肯定是还没出柜
Dude's a totally closet case
除了他的衣着 还有
Okay,what else can you tell me about the guy
其他什么吗
Other than...his outfit
他给猫带了一个粗麻袋
He was carrying a burlap sack for the cats
他要猫干什么的
What does he want with the cats
真舒服 我怎么知道 但是他把猫全带走了
Atta boy.Hell if I know,but he took all of them
有一只被他吃了
Except for the one he ate
什么
What
我们要找的凶手牙口不错
Apparently our guy's a sweet tooth
小猫咪都不在话下
For kitty cats
麻袋上面有写字
And the sack had something written on it
上面写的什么
Okay,what did it say
喂 我们说好的
Hey,come on,we had a deal
你跟这大个子说说
Well,you tell that to the tall drink
是他先停下的
He's the one who stopped rubbing
Sam
我手都抽筋了
Hand cramps
它不吭声了
She's not talking
这就对了
Atta boy
上面写着前卫餐厅 你走运了
It said Avant-Garde Cuisine.Lucky for you
我看得懂法语
I read French
那是主街道上的一家餐厅
That's a cafe on Main Street
宠物不得入内
No dogs allowed
怪不得他身上有汉堡包味道和洗洁精的味道
No wonder he smelled like hamburgers and dish soap
我们要进城一趟了
So,we got to go downtown
显然我们要找的人在餐厅里工作
Apparantly our guy works at a restaurant
嗯
Yeah
等等等
Wait,wait,wait
你们确定不收养我吗
Sure you don't want to adopt me
不需要 谢谢
No thanks.We'll pass
别走 我不会舔脚的
No,I'm not above licking feet
嘿 大个子 回来
Hey,big'un,come back here
好了
All right
等等
Hey hold up
怎么了
What's the matter
我试过的最舒服的挠挠
Best belly rub I ever had
自由啦
Freedom
我给动物管理中心留了个惊喜
I left a superise in there for animal control
我不知道你还是个傻子
I didn't peg you for a softy
回家了回家了
Going home,I'm going home
宝贝儿我回来了
Honey I'm coming home
回家了
Yeah,I'm coming home
烟肉 烟肉 烟肉
Bacon!Bacon!Bacon!Bacon
我想问
I'm sorry
谁家这么有钱 星期一都不营业
Who can afford to be closed on Monday these days
-杀人的疯子 -对
-A homicide maniac -Yeah
这边
Hey
看
Check this out
Leo警长
Chef Leo
是他吗
Think he's our guy
这里是乡下
It's okie town
很多男的都戴牛仔帽
Lots of dudes were cowboy hats
羟可酮 曲马多 美沙酮
Oh,oxycodone,tramadol,methadone
注 均有止痛的功效
看来他喜欢舒舒服服的麻木着
Guess he likes to cook comfortably numb
嗯 对
Yeah,apparently
-救命 -请救救我们 先生
-Help us -Please mister
在这里
Over here
你听到了吗
Did you hear that
好像小孩儿的声音
Sound like little kids
救命 如果你不救我们
Help!If you don't free us
-主厨会吃了我们的 -它说的是真的
-The chef will eat us -She's not lying
我们在笼子里
We're in the cage
吃了你们
Eat you
看看你身后的冰箱
Look at the refrigerator behind you
是的 在你身后
Yeah,behind you
在冰箱里
In the fridge
嘿
Hey
猫头鹰脑袋
Owl brains
猎豹肝脏
Cheetah liver
灰熊心脏
Grizzly heart
咒语书
A spell book
萨满教
Shamanism
主厨要用巫术来干嘛
What's the chef doing dabbling with witchcraft
这里写着 不管你吃下动物的任何器官
It says here,whatever animal organs you ingest
正确地混合巫毒和香料
With the right mix of hoo doo and spices
你就能暂时获得该动物的能力
You temporarily gain the power of that animal
那么
So,okay
如果你吃了猫头鹰大脑
If you're munching on owl brains
你的脑袋就能转的跟驱魔人一样了
Your head spins around like The Exorcist
差不多
Close
可以让你的IQ激增
Bolsters your IQ,okay
吃下猎豹肝脏就能获得速度
Eat a cheetah liver for speed
灰熊心脏获得力量
Bear heart for strength
如果他吃了这些东西
Okay,so if he's chowing down on this stuff
这样就能解释
Then it'd make sense,why he
他为什么会勒死标本制作商
Constricted the taxidermist
还挠死了收留中心的那个家伙
And clawed the guy in the shelter
别见怪 为什么会有人想吃你们呢
Oh,no offense,but why do we want to eat you guys
-呃 我们脊椎可折叠 -是啊 相信我们
-Uh,we have collapsable spine -We do,promise
看看这里
Look at this
狮子肝脏加上鹰的心脏
Lion liver plus eagle heart
响尾蛇的獠牙加上蟒蛇的膀胱
Rattlesnake fangs plus anaconda bladder
他在混合各种器官
He's mixing ingredients
小声点
Shoo!Quiet
别嘘我 你安静点
Don't shush me!You be quiet
我很安静
I am quite.Now
你们是谁
Who the hell are you
我们是卫生局的
We're from the health department
过来检查卫生
Stopped by for an inspection
我不知道我们有安排检查
I wasn't aware we had one scheduled
是的 没有 这才是重点
Yeah,no,you wouldn't be,that's the point
不是说你们下班了吗
Besides,I thought you're closed
下班了呀 不过主厨在进行私人就餐
We are,Chef's having a private dinner
事实上 他随时会过来的
In fact,he'll be here in any minute
那好吧 既然这样
Oh,well then,in that case
关闭厨房
Kitchen's shut down
关闭 为什么
Shut down?Why
因为你们都违反了刑法第八章第十四项条例
Because you're both in clear violation of penal code 8.14
出去 快点
Out,come on,get out
都给我出去
Both of you
有什么事儿会通知你们的
We'll let you know
好了 我去前门 你去后门
All right,I take the front,you take the back
我们都不知道怎么杀死这家伙
We don't even know how to kill this guy
朝他脑袋开一枪
Empty one of these in his head
看看怎么样
See what that does
变色龙 味道也不坏
Chameleons,aren't that bad
尝起来有点像鸡肉
Kind of taste like chicken
你是怎么做到的
How the hell did you do that
-做什么 -别装了
-Do what? -Don't play coy
我想知道你是什么
I wanna know what you are
去他的章鱼鲨
Oh,screw the sharktopus
你是我的主菜
You're my main course
为什么这里有狗的味道
Why does it smell like dog in here
味道是从你身上来的
That smell's coming from you
所有的狗都应该被系上项圈拴起来
All dog should be leashed
你对我弟弟做了什么
What did you do to my brother
你弟弟吗
Your brother
你妈妈怀你们俩的时候
What was your mom smoking
到底磕了什么药
When she had you two
他没事
He's fine
只是在晚饭前小憩一下罢了
He's just taking a little cat-nap before dinner
我从没吃过人类心脏
I've never had human heart before
听说挺难嚼的
Heard it's a bit chewy
幸好我不怎么挑食
Good job I'm not a fussy eater
你绝对是有病
You're sick
经常有人这么说
Told that once or twice
不不 不是指你心理变态
No,no,not in the head I
呃 你确实有点儿变态
Well,you're that,too,but
但我说的是 像癌症那种病
I mean sick like cancer
看来狗真的什么都闻得出来
Oh,I guess dog really can sniff it out
癌症第四期
Stage four carcinoma
所以你才做了这些事
So that's why you're doing this
发生什么事了
What happened
倒霉到家 决定放手一搏吗
Draw a short straw,decided to break bed
当我被确诊的时候
So when I was diagnosed
正常的治疗过程已经无法治好我了
I was way past standard treatment
没人能救我
No one could save me
但是有了个波尼族萨满的帮助
But then with a help of a Pawnee Shaman
以及一张动物园年卡 我找到了疗法
And a zoo membership,I found a cure
只是暂时性的
Would be the temporally one
癌症总会复发
Cancer always came back
所以你开始用各种器官做实验吗
You're starting experimenting with different organs,huh
给自己混了一大盘子肉当解药吃是吗
Taking a single serving for a combo platter
我还能说什么呢
What can I say
结合各种疗法是有效的
Combination therapy works
我变得更强壮 而且效果
I felt stronger,and the effect
持续很长
Lasted longer
所以你就觉得自己可以随意杀人了是吗
And if you smoke a few innocent people in the process
哦没错 因为你自我感觉超级良好
Well hell,at least you felt better
我没想杀人的
I didn't mean to kill anyone
本来没想杀
At first
但如果有人挡了我的路
But if people got in my way
他们就变成了附带损害品
They became collateral damage
我猜你干掉的猎食者已经够多了
Guess you've eaten enough predators
多到自己也开始变成猎食者了
Start to become one
人如其食 对吧
You're what you eat,right
即使你真的通过这样的方式 获得了别人的力量
You really think the power you hold over people's lives
也无法弥补你本身的缺陷
Can make up for what you lack in your own
那么 狗崽子
So,dog boy
我要吃下什么才能打倒你呢
What do I need to eat to take you down
你不会想这么做的
You don't wanna do this
哦 但我确实想这么做
Oh,but I do want to do this
看 我会杀了你
See,I'm gonna kill you
引起食欲
Work up a nice appetite
然后 我会吃了你弟弟
And then,I'm gonna eat your brother
虽然我不知道他到底是什么东西
I mean I don't know what the hell he is
但是 有那么强大的治愈能力
But with healing powers like that
谁在乎呢
Who cares
我要他治愈的能力
He could cure me
犬科
Dog on
都差不多
Sort of dog
抱歉 狼胜过狗
Sorry,wolf trumps dog
可能吧 但不能胜过一群狗
Maybe,but not a whole pack
嘿
Hey
看在上帝份上
For the love of God
Sammy
Zeke
你们俩随便谁赶紧给我醒一个
Whoever the hell you are
嘿 快醒醒
Hey,Come on
别逼我舔你脸
Don't make me lick your damn face
嘿
Hey
来吧
Come on
你给我们打电话说领养的事的时候
When you called us about adopting
我们不能相信
We couldn't believe it
你真是个小甜甜
Aren't you a sweet ass
离远点 愚蠢的人类
Back off,tofu breathe
你一定饿坏了
You must be starving
你很幸运 我烤了一些培根狗狗蛋糕
Lucky for you,I baked some bacon doggy cupcake
我跟着这两个人 会拉出芽草的
I'm gonna be pooping wheatgrass with this two
看 我知道他们是嬉皮士怪胎
Look,I know they are hippie freaks
但他们能给你一个好家
But they are going to give you a good home
那是你应得的
One you deserve
是啊 是啊
Yeah,yeah
真希望能带你上路 但是
Wish we could take you on the road with this,but
那不是给狗的好生活
It's no life for a dog
算了吧
Don't sweat it
反正我晕车
I got car sick anyway
我之前没敢告诉你
I was afraid to tell you earlier
我吐你车后座上了
But I barfed in your back seat
你
You
怎么了
What
我会想你的 伙计
I'm gonna miss you,buddy
我也会想你的
I'll miss you,too
顺便说一下
And by the way
作为一个具有狗的荣誉称号的人 你应该知道
As an honorary dog,there is something you should know
狗其实不是人类最好的朋友
Dogs aren't really man's best friend
你说什么呢
What are you talking about
我知道这听起来像是阴谋论者的论调
I know it sounds like a conspiracy theory
但是我们在这里的真正原因是
But the real reason we were put here was to
是什么
Put here to do what
开什么玩笑
Oh,you got to be kidding me
咒语现在失效了
Now the spell wears off
好吧
Okay
怎么样
How did it go
坏消息是 我会想那个家伙的
Well,bad news is I'm gonna miss the flea bag
好消息是 咒语终于失效了
Good news is it looks like the spell finally wears off
你还好吧
You okay
那凶手把你揍得挺惨
The Stetson man got you pretty good
是啊 我很好
Yeah,I'm fine
我就是
I just
我在想他说的话 没法停下
I can't stop thinking what he said
算了吧 Sammy
Come on,Sammy
那货脑子有泡
The guy was out of his freaking gourd
是 但是 我是说 为什么
Yeah,but,I mean why
他为什么会那么问
Why would he asked that
为什么想知道我是什么
Why did he wanna know what I was
谁知道呢
Who the hell knows
他整个人都不正常
He's all jacked up on juice you know
他被他不能控制的东西附身了
He was possessed by something he couldn't control
那是
It was
失控只是时间问题
It's a matter of time before it completely took over
你不能跟疯子讲道理 是吧
You can't reason with crazy,right
我不知道
I don't know
我知道
Well,I do
相信我 Sammy 你没什么可担心的
Trust me,Sammy,you got nothing to worry about